https://followthecamino.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
×
[ninja_form id=91]
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Follow the Camino is in compliance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2002 and the EU General Data Protection Regulation of 2018. We aim to take a responsible approach to all areas of our business. In order to process your booking, we need to collect certain personal details from you on the online booking form, or other information forms, such as the names and addresses of party members, credit/debit card or other payment details and special requirements such as those relating to any disability or medical condition which may affect the chosen holiday arrangements. We may, from time to time, need to ask you for more personal information. We may need to pass on your personal details to supplier companies and organisations that we work with (for example your hotel or other trip service providers) on a need-to-know basis, so that your holiday can be catered for as required.
Apart from the exceptions outlined above, we will keep all the personal details that you give us in connection with your holiday absolutely confidential and secure. We do not sell or pass on for marketing purposes any information you give to us. We may, from time to time, contact you with information about One Foot Abroad and/or Follow the Camino, however you will be asked to opt in to receive such communications. If you do not wish to receive any such information, please inform us or click on the Unsubscribe button at the end of our email newsletters. Both One Foot Abroad, Follow the Camino, Flexi-trip and the internet service providers that host our sites, strive to maintain appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you to make your holiday booking.
When you purchase a holiday online you do so through a secure server. The use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology means that all personal information – such as your credit card number – will be encrypted as it travels from your computer to the Company Booking Engine. When received, the information is decrypted and processed in the same way as a normal credit card transaction by telephone. The information will be used to process the full payment 60 days prior to departure, unless advised otherwise.
If you wish to ascertain what information One Foot Abroad and or Follow the Camino holds about you, please email us at info@followthecamino.com
Cookies
The cookies this website uses are below:
Google Analytics: Allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, referral source and length of time spent on website. The information is de-personalised and is displayed only as numbers, this means it can’t be tracked back to actual individuals. This helps protect your privacy. By using Google Analytics we see which content is most popular on our website so we can strive to give you more of the things you enjoy.
Google AdWords: Enables us to see which of our ads led to traffic and subsequently lead to contact form submissions. This helps us to understand who might be interested in our services so we can serve them better with relevant ads.
Facebook Advertising: We use Facebook advertising conversion tracking and re-targeting pixels, which allows us to collect and receive information from Facebook or elsewhere on the internet and use it to provide measurement services to target our advertising.
Social sharing cookies:
On our blog we use social sharing buttons for services including, but not limited to, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+ and Facebook. This allows you to share pages with your friends via those networks. Whilst you will be asked to login to use these services, this process is handled directly with the social sharing providers and their databases and servers. These sites may also monitor your usage of these buttons, through the use of external tracking codes that are required to run the buttons on this website.
Email codes
If you have opted in to receive our newsletters, then this may include tracking codes that help us understand who, as well as how many people have opened or clicked on each email. This data helps us to create better emails in the future, and provide you with a better service. This data is stored on the servers of our email partners and covered under their security measures.
Links to other websites
This website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over the other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Links
Hyperlinks on this site may be shortened. The purpose of which is to hide long links for functionality and tracking purposes.
Search for:
Search
Get FREE Camino de Santiago tips
Sign up for our weekly newsletter and be the first to hear about new products, events and exclusive offers.
Select Country
Australia (+61)Canada (+1)Ireland (+353)New Zealand (+64)South Africa (+27)United Kingdom (+44)United States (+1)Aaland Islands (+358)Afghanistan (+93)Albania (+355)Algeria (+213)Andorra (+376)Angola (+244)Anguilla (+1264)Antigua
Barbuda (+1268)Argentina (+54)Armenia (+374)Aruba (+297)Austria (+43)Azerbaijan (+994)Bahamas (+1242)Bahrain (+973)Bangladesh (+880)Barbados (+1246)Belarus (+375)Belgium (+32)Belize (+501)Benin (+229)Bermuda (+1441)Bhutan (+975)Bolivia (+591)Bosnia Herzegovina (+387)Botswana (+267)Brazil (+55)Brunei (+673)Bulgaria (+359)Burkina Faso (+226)Burundi (+257)Cambodia (+855)Cameroon (+237)Cape Verde Islands (+238)Cayman Islands (+1345)Central African Republic (+236)Chile (+56)China (+86)Colombia (+57)Comoros (+269)Congo (+242)Cook Islands (+682)Costa Rica (+506)Croatia (+385)Cuba (+53)Cyprus North (+90392)Cyprus South (+357)Czech Republic (+42)Denmark (+45)Djibouti (+253)Dominica (+1809)Dominican Republic (+1809)Ecuador (+593)Egypt (+20)El Salvador (+503)Equatorial Guinea (+240)Eritrea (+291)Estonia (+372)Ethiopia (+251)Falkland Islands (+500)Faroe Islands (+298)Fiji (+679)Finland (+358)France (+33)French Guiana (+594)French Polynesia (+689)Gabon (+241)Gambia (+220)Georgia (+7880)Germany (+49)Ghana (+233)Gibraltar (+350)Greece (+30)Greenland (+299)Grenada (+1473)Guadeloupe (+590)Guam (+671)Guatemala (+502)Guinea (+224)Guinea - Bissau (+245)Guyana (+592)Haiti (+509)Honduras (+504)Hong Kong (+852)Hungary (+36)Iceland (+354)India (+91)Indonesia (+62)Iran (+98)Iraq (+964)Israel (+972)Italy (+39)Jamaica (+1876)Japan (+81)Jordan (+962)Kazakhstan (+7)Kenya (+254)Kiribati (+686)Korea North (+850)Korea South (+82)Kuwait (+965)Kyrgyzstan (+996)Laos (+856)Latvia (+371)Lebanon (+961)Lesotho (+266)Liberia (+231)Libya (+218)Liechtenstein (+417)Lithuania (+370)Luxembourg (+352)Macao (+853)Macedonia (+389)Madagascar (+261)Malawi (+265)Malaysia (+60)Maldives (+960)Mali (+223)Malta (+356)Marshall Islands (+692)Martinique (+596)Mauritania (+222)Mauritius (+230)Mayotte (+269)Mexico (+52)Micronesia (+691)Moldova (+373)Monaco (+377)Mongolia (+976)Montserrat (+1664)Morocco (+212)Mozambique (+258)Myanmar (+95)Namibia (+264)Nauru (+674)Nepal (+977)Netherlands (+31)New Caledonia (+687)Nicaragua (+505)Niger (+227)Nigeria (+234)Niue (+683)Norfolk Islands (+672)Northern Marianas (+670)Norway (+47)Oman (+968)Pakistan (+92)Palau (+680)Palestine (+970)Panama (+507)Papua New Guinea (+675)Paraguay (+595)Peru (+51)Philippines (+63)Poland (+48)Portugal (+351)Puerto Rico (+1787)Qatar (+974)Reunion (+262)Romania (+40)Russia (+7)Rwanda (+250)San Marino (+378)Sao Tome
Principe (+239)Saudi Arabia (+966)Senegal (+221)Serbia (+381)Seychelles (+248)Sierra Leone (+232)Singapore (+65)Slovakia (+421)Slovenia (+386)Solomon Islands (+677)Somalia (+252)Spain (+34)Sri Lanka (+94)St. Helena (+290)St. Kitts (+1869)St. Lucia (+1758)Sudan (+249)Suriname (+597)Swaziland (+268)Sweden (+46)Switzerland (+41)Syria (+963)Taiwan (+886)Tajikstan (+7)Tanzania (+225)Thailand (+66)Togo (+228)Tonga (+676)Trinidad and Tobago (+1868)Tunisia (+216)Turkey (+90)Turkmenistan (+993)Turks
Caicos Islands (+1649)Tuvalu (+688)Uganda (+256)Ukraine (+380)United Arab Emirates (+971)Uruguay (+598)Uzbekistan (+7)Vanuatu (+678)Vatican City (+379)Venezuela (+58)Vietnam (+84)Virgin Islands - British (+84)Virgin Islands - US (+84)Wallis
Futuna (+681)Yemen (North) (+969)Yemen (South) (+967)Zambia (+260)Zimbabwe (+263)
I accept the Privacy Policy*.
Subscribe
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. Learn more.Got it!
Book Now
×
Start Planning Now!
Preferred Month & Year
Month
January
February
March
April
May
June
Select Country
Australia (+61)Canada (+1)Ireland (+353)New Zealand (+64)South Africa (+27)United Kingdom (+44)United States (+1)Aaland Islands (+358)Afghanistan (+93)Albania (+355)Algeria (+213)Andorra (+376)Angola (+244)Anguilla (+1264)Antigua
Barbuda (+1268)Argentina (+54)Armenia (+374)Aruba (+297)Austria (+43)Azerbaijan (+994)Bahamas (+1242)Bahrain (+973)Bangladesh (+880)Barbados (+1246)Belarus (+375)Belgium (+32)Belize (+501)Benin (+229)Bermuda (+1441)Bhutan (+975)Bolivia (+591)Bosnia Herzegovina (+387)Botswana (+267)Brazil (+55)Brunei (+673)Bulgaria (+359)Burkina Faso (+226)Burundi (+257)Cambodia (+855)Cameroon (+237)Cape Verde Islands (+238)Cayman Islands (+1345)Central African Republic (+236)Chile (+56)China (+86)Colombia (+57)Comoros (+269)Congo (+242)Cook Islands (+682)Costa Rica (+506)Croatia (+385)Cuba (+53)Cyprus North (+90392)Cyprus South (+357)Czech Republic (+42)Denmark (+45)Djibouti (+253)Dominica (+1809)Dominican Republic (+1809)Ecuador (+593)Egypt (+20)El Salvador (+503)Equatorial Guinea (+240)Eritrea (+291)Estonia (+372)Ethiopia (+251)Falkland Islands (+500)Faroe Islands (+298)Fiji (+679)Finland (+358)France (+33)French Guiana (+594)French Polynesia (+689)Gabon (+241)Gambia (+220)Georgia (+7880)Germany (+49)Ghana (+233)Gibraltar (+350)Greece (+30)Greenland (+299)Grenada (+1473)Guadeloupe (+590)Guam (+671)Guatemala (+502)Guinea (+224)Guinea - Bissau (+245)Guyana (+592)Haiti (+509)Honduras (+504)Hong Kong (+852)Hungary (+36)Iceland (+354)India (+91)Indonesia (+62)Iran (+98)Iraq (+964)Israel (+972)Italy (+39)Jamaica (+1876)Japan (+81)Jordan (+962)Kazakhstan (+7)Kenya (+254)Kiribati (+686)Korea North (+850)Korea South (+82)Kuwait (+965)Kyrgyzstan (+996)Laos (+856)Latvia (+371)Lebanon (+961)Lesotho (+266)Liberia (+231)Libya (+218)Liechtenstein (+417)Lithuania (+370)Luxembourg (+352)Macao (+853)Macedonia (+389)Madagascar (+261)Malawi (+265)Malaysia (+60)Maldives (+960)Mali (+223)Malta (+356)Marshall Islands (+692)Martinique (+596)Mauritania (+222)Mauritius (+230)Mayotte (+269)Mexico (+52)Micronesia (+691)Moldova (+373)Monaco (+377)Mongolia (+976)Montserrat (+1664)Morocco (+212)Mozambique (+258)Myanmar (+95)Namibia (+264)Nauru (+674)Nepal (+977)Netherlands (+31)New Caledonia (+687)Nicaragua (+505)Niger (+227)Nigeria (+234)Niue (+683)Norfolk Islands (+672)Northern Marianas (+670)Norway (+47)Oman (+968)Pakistan (+92)Palau (+680)Palestine (+970)Panama (+507)Papua New Guinea (+675)Paraguay (+595)Peru (+51)Philippines (+63)Poland (+48)Portugal (+351)Puerto Rico (+1787)Qatar (+974)Reunion (+262)Romania (+40)Russia (+7)Rwanda (+250)San Marino (+378)Sao Tome
Principe (+239)Saudi Arabia (+966)Senegal (+221)Serbia (+381)Seychelles (+248)Sierra Leone (+232)Singapore (+65)Slovakia (+421)Slovenia (+386)Solomon Islands (+677)Somalia (+252)Spain (+34)Sri Lanka (+94)St. Helena (+290)St. Kitts (+1869)St. Lucia (+1758)Sudan (+249)Suriname (+597)Swaziland (+268)Sweden (+46)Switzerland (+41)Syria (+963)Taiwan (+886)Tajikstan (+7)Tanzania (+225)Thailand (+66)Togo (+228)Tonga (+676)Trinidad and Tobago (+1868)Tunisia (+216)Turkey (+90)Turkmenistan (+993)Turks
Caicos Islands (+1649)Tuvalu (+688)Uganda (+256)Ukraine (+380)United Arab Emirates (+971)Uruguay (+598)Uzbekistan (+7)Vanuatu (+678)Vatican City (+379)Venezuela (+58)Vietnam (+84)Virgin Islands - British (+84)Virgin Islands - US (+84)Wallis
Futuna (+681)Yemen (North) (+969)Yemen (South) (+967)Zambia (+260)Zimbabwe (+263)
I accept the Privacy Policy*.
I accept to receive communication from Follow the Camino
How should we contact you?
Phone
Email
Enquire Now
